Support Admin Watch on kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
دعم المشرف شاهد على kissasia.cam أو kisskh.org
♪Blossoms rise and scatter never to return♪
♪تزهر الأزهار وتنتشر دون أن تعود♪
♪Time rushes on toward its withering end♪
♪الوقت يتسارع نحو نهايته الذابلة♪
♪Rights and wrongs unfold♪
♪الصواب والخطأ يتكشفان♪
♪Breaking through fate's tightening walls♪
♪اختراق جدران القدر المشددة♪
♪Few ever find their way home♪
♪قليلون هم من يجدون طريقهم إلى المنزل♪
♪Through storms and drifting snow as silver hair falls♪
♪من خلال العواصف والثلوج المتساقطة بينما يتساقط الشعر الفضي♪
♪A lifetime of ruin for one bitter revel♪
♪حياة من الخراب من أجل احتفال مرير واحد♪
♪A single dream born from a single thought♪
♪حلم واحد ولد من فكرة واحدة♪
♪Shattered at a touch♪
♪تحطم عند لمسة♪
♪When the dream fades I look once more♪
♪عندما يتلاشى الحلم أنظر مرة أخرى♪
=Aligned Reverence=
=الاحترام المتوافق=
(Adapted from Jinyi's novel of the same name on Qimao Novel)
(مقتبس من رواية جيني التي تحمل نفس الاسم على Qimao Novel)
=Episode 5= (I will be with you)
=الحلقة 5= (سأكون معك)
(Heaven Rewards Diligence)
(الجنة تكافئ الاجتهاد)
Young Master Xie.
السيد الشاب شيه.
I made a new set of clothes for you.
لقد صنعت لك مجموعة جديدة من الملابس.
The fabric is soft and gentle.
القماش ناعم ولطيف.
Best for recovery and health.
الأفضل للتعافي والصحة.
Come out and take it.
تعال وخذها.
Alright.
على ما يرام.
You may leave it outside.
يمكنك تركه بالخارج.
What is wrong?
ما هو الخطأ؟
Nothing.
لا شئ.
I was applying medicine.
كنت أطبق الطب.
Young Master Xie.
السيد الشاب شيه.
Are you alright?
هل انت بخير؟
Let me help you.
دعني أساعدك.
I can do it myself.
أستطيع أن أفعل ذلك بنفسي.
It is fine.
إنه بخير.
The dignified Sixth Young Master Xie,
السيد الشاب السادس المحترم شيه،
yet so badly injured,
ومع ذلك أصيب بجروح بالغة،
and still refusing help like this.
وما زال يرفض المساعدة مثل هذه.
Are you embarrassed, or afraid of pain?
هل تشعر بالحرج أو الخوف من الألم؟
If you will not let me apply it,
إذا لم تسمح لي بتطبيقه،
I will tell Grandmother and Mother.
سأخبر جدتي وأمي.
They can come apply it for you.
يمكنهم أن يأتوا لتطبيقه لك.
No, wait.
لا، انتظر.
Fine.
بخير.
If it hurts,
إذا كان الأمر مؤلمًا،
call out.
نداء.
There is no shame in it.
لا عيب في ذلك .
I have yet to ask you,
لم أسألك بعد
your injury,
إصابتك،
has it healed?
هل شُفي؟
I am fine.
أنا بخير.
It no longer troubles me.
لم يعد يقلقني.
Here.
هنا.
You must not do this anymore.
لا يجب عليك فعل هذا بعد الآن.
Always enduring injuries in silence,
تحمل الإصابات دائمًا في صمت،
holding back the pain,
كبح الألم،
and saying it does not hurt.
والقول أنه لا يضر.
But you,
ولكن انت
are you not the same?
هل أنت لست نفس الشيء؟
I lost my parents at a young age.
لقد فقدت والدي في سن مبكرة.
I have eaten enough bitterness.
لقد أكلت ما يكفي من المرارة.
So pain no longer feels like pain.
لذلك لم يعد الألم يبدو وكأنه ألم.
That was before my elder brother and I appeared.
وكان ذلك قبل ظهوري أنا وأخي الأكبر.
From now on, I will protect you.
من الآن فصاعدا، سأحميك.
It is I who has failed the Xiao family.
أنا الذي خذلت عائلة شياو.
I am unworthy of such kindness.
أنا لا أستحق مثل هذا اللطف.
I only wish...
أتمنى فقط...
Enough.
كافٍ.
Let me help you.
دعني أساعدك.
I can manage on my own.
أنا قادر على إدارة أموري بنفسي.
I have put it away for you.
لقد وضعته بعيدا عنك.
Su Jinyuan.
سو جينيوان.
I know you struggle to forgive yourself.
أعلم أنك تكافح من أجل مسامحة نفسك.
But to me,
ولكن بالنسبة لي،
you are the one most worthy.
أنت الأكثر استحقاقا.
Thank you,
شكرًا لك،
Xie Yunyan.
شيه يونيان.
The bougainvilleas are blooming beautifully.
تزدهر نباتات الجهنمية بشكل جميل.
Look.
ينظر.
Yes.
نعم.
Grand Madam, Madam.
سيدتي الكبرى، سيدتي.
What is the matter?
ما المشكلة؟
The General and the Young General
الجنرال والجنرال الشاب
have fallen in battle for the nation.
لقد سقطوا في معركة من أجل الأمة.
Impossible.
مستحيل.
Impossible!
مستحيل!
(Memorial Tablet of Xiao Jin)
(لوح تذكاري لشياو جين)
(Xiao Manor)
(قصر شياو)
Sixth son of the Xiao family, Xie Yunyan,
شيه يونيان، الابن السادس لعائلة شياو .
brings father and brother home.
يحضر الأب والأخ إلى المنزل.
(Xiao Manor)
(قصر شياو)
(Memorial Tablet of Xiao Jin)
(لوح تذكاري لشياو جين)
Jin.
إحساس.
Yunxi.
يونكسي.
Yunxin.
يونشين.
You are home.
أنت في المنزل.
Home at last.
البيت أخيرا.
(Xiao Manor)
(قصر شياو)
Their spirits have not yet dispersed.
ولم تتفرق أرواحهم بعد.
Their remains return home.
وتعود رفاتهم إلى الوطن.
Welcome the General and the Young General
مرحبا بالجنرال والجنرال الشاب
back to the manor!
العودة إلى القصر!
The garrison received a secret order.
تلقت الحامية أمراً سرياً.
It is suspected that the Xiao father and son may have faked their deaths.
ويُشتبه في أن الأب والابن شياو ربما زيفا وفاتهما.
We are ordered to investigate.
لقد أُمرنا بالتحقيق.
Open the coffins for examination.
افتح التوابيت للفحص.
Today is the day
اليوم هو اليوم
our departed return home.
رحيلنا يعود إلى الوطن.
His Majesty granted this.
وقد منح جلالته هذا.
The order you follow,
الترتيب الذي تتبعه،
from whom does it come?
من أين يأتي هذا؟
The Xiao father and son died without cause.
مات الأب والابن شياو بدون سبب.
You hinder us at every step.
أنت تعيقنا في كل خطوة.
Clearly something is amiss
من الواضح أن هناك شيئا خاطئا
within these coffins.
داخل هذه التوابيت.
Open them.
افتحهم.
Yes.
نعم.
If you wish to open them,
إذا كنت ترغب في فتحها،
you must step over my body first.
يجب عليك أن تتخطى جسدي أولاً.
Any who obstruct
أي شخص يعيق
shall be killed without mercy.
يجب قتله بلا رحمة.
The case of Linchuan remains unsettled.
تظل قضية لينشوان دون حل.
Sir Luo, do you intend to exterminate the Xiao family on your own authority?
سيد لوه، هل تنوي إبادة عائلة شياو بناءً على سلطتك الخاصة؟
Stand aside.
قف جانبا.
Xie Yunyan.
شيه يونيان.
Open the coffin.
افتح التابوت
You wretched dog.
يا لك من كلب بائس.
Do you truly think the Xiao family has no one left?
هل تعتقد حقًا أن عائلة شياو لم يتبق لها أحد؟
(To the General of the Northern Cavalry. A matter of utmost secrecy.)
(إلى جنرال سلاح الفرسان الشمالي. مسألة سرية للغاية.)
(They forged a secret letter accusing the Xiao family of treason.)
(قاموا بتزوير رسالة سرية تتهم عائلة شياو بالخيانة.)
The coffin opening is but a pretense.
إن فتح التابوت ما هو إلا ذريعة.
To frame the Xiao family is the truth.
إن إيقاع عائلة شياو في الفخ هو الحقيقة.
Even if it costs my life today,
حتى لو كلفني ذلك حياتي اليوم،
I will kill you.
سأقتلك.
Xie Yunyan.
شيه يونيان.
Let go.
اتركه.
He is not worth it.
إنه لا يستحق ذلك.
Would you risk your life again
هل تخاطر بحياتك مرة أخرى؟
for a villain, and let the Xiao family lose you too?
من أجل الشرير، ودع عائلة شياو تخسرك أيضًا؟
Then I will ask His Majesty myself.
ثم سأسأل جلالته بنفسي.
In this world,
في هذا العالم،
where lies justice?
أين تكمن العدالة؟
(Zichen Gate)
(بوابة زيتشن)
The Xiao family suffers unjust accusations.
عائلة شياو تعاني من اتهامات ظالمة.
Their loyal spirits cannot rest.
أرواحهم المخلصة لا تستطيع أن ترتاح.
We swear to clear our name.
نحن نقسم على تبرئة اسمنا.
Let heaven and earth bear witness.
لتشهد السماء والأرض.
I will stand with you.
سأقف معك.
One strike of the grievance drum
ضربة واحدة لطبل التظلم
means one must shed blood to seek justice.
يعني أنه يجب سفك الدماء من أجل تحقيق العدالة.
Are you certain?
هل انت متأكد؟
The Xiao family suffers unjust accusations.
عائلة شياو تعاني من اتهامات ظالمة.
Their loyal spirits cannot rest.
أرواحهم المخلصة لا تستطيع أن ترتاح.
We swear to clear our name.
نحن نقسم على تبرئة اسمنا.
Let heaven and earth bear witness.
لتشهد السماء والأرض.
♪Even the gentlest waves can never be your touch♪
♪حتى الأمواج الأكثر لطفًا لا يمكنها أبدًا أن تصل إلى لمستك♪
♪No lighthouse waiting ever matched the way I held on♪
♪لم يسبق أن قارنا بين منارة الانتظار والطريقة التي تمسكت بها♪
♪The harbor lies in silent moonlight♪
♪الميناء يقع في ضوء القمر الصامت♪
♪The pipes call no seabirds home♪
♪الأنابيب لا تدعو الطيور البحرية إلى المنزل♪
♪This coastal line feels barren as a wasteland♪
♪يبدو هذا الخط الساحلي قاحلًا كأرض قاحلة♪
♪They laugh at those who carve their hopes into drifting boats♪
♪إنهم يضحكون على أولئك الذين ينحتون آمالهم في قوارب عائمة♪
♪Yet in my loneliest nights you never reached for me♪
♪ولكن في ليالي الوحدة لم تقترب مني أبدًا♪
♪At the far edge of the tides I waited long for you♪
♪في أقصى حافة المد والجزر انتظرتك طويلاً♪
♪Seasons washed away by ebb and flow but still I never left♪
♪مرت الفصول بالمد والجزر ولكنني لم أغادر أبدًا♪
♪A gentle breeze slips through mirage and illusion♪
♪نسيمة لطيفة تتسلل عبر السراب والوهم♪
♪Even starlight's tender message pales beside your single greeting♪
♪حتى رسالة ضوء النجوم الرقيقة تتضاءل أمام تحيتك الوحيدة♪
♪At the far edge of the tides I waited long for you♪
♪في أقصى حافة المد والجزر انتظرتك طويلاً♪
♪Longing lets the monsoon wrinkle time as I run to you♪
♪الشوق يجعل الرياح الموسمية تتجعد الوقت وأنا أركض إليك♪
♪Snow may turn one's hair to white yet I burn all bridges for you♪
♪قد يحوّل الثلج شعر الإنسان إلى اللون الأبيض، ولكنني أحرق كل الجسور من أجلك♪
♪When the sea calms after the storm I will see you turning back♪
♪عندما يهدأ البحر بعد العاصفة سأراك تعود ♪
♪At the far edge of the tides I waited long for you♪
♪في أقصى حافة المد والجزر انتظرتك طويلاً♪
♪Seasons washed away by ebb and flow but still I never left♪
♪مرت الفصول بالمد والجزر ولكنني لم أغادر أبدًا♪
♪A gentle breeze slips through mirage and illusion♪
♪نسيمة لطيفة تتسلل عبر السراب والوهم♪
♪When the sea calms after the storm I will see you turning back♪
♪عندما يهدأ البحر بعد العاصفة سأراك تعود ♪